http://www.texansgab.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Sports Gab Network knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy covers Sports Gab Network’s treatment of personal information that Sports Gab Network gathers when you are on any Sports Gab Network website and when you use Sports Gab Network services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Sports Gab Network does not own or control, or to individuals that Sports Gab Network does not employ or manage.
Information Collected by Sports Gab Network
We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our websites. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Sports Gab Network users:
1. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our websites or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.
2. Automatic Information:
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Sports Gab Network and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Sports Gab Network cookie information, and the page you requested. Sports Gab Network uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.
Sports Gab Network may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.
Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Sports Gab Network will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.
E-mail Communications
Sports Gab Network is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. Sports Gab Network may send out e-mails with Sports Gab Network-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our websites are visited and by how many people. Sports Gab Network cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.
The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Sports Gab Network’s coolest features.
Sports Gab Network’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Sharing Your Information
Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.
Sports Gab Network Personnel: Sports Gab Network personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Sports Gab Network business.
Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Sports Gab Network, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.
Protection of Sports Gab Network and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Sports Gab Network, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Syndication: Sports Gab Network allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Sports Gab Network website.
With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.
Children Under 18 Years of Age
You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Sports Gab Network websites. As a result, Sports Gab Network does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Sports Gab Network has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using Sports Gab Network or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Sports Gab Network may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Sports Gab Network website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.
Conditions of Use
If you decide to visit any of the Sports Gab Network websites, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.
Effective Date of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of 08/11/06 and last updated 06/16/11.
Recent Posts
Texans Waive Veteran Wide Out Kenny Stills
McNair Says Texans Will Speak to Offensive and Defensive Coaches to Be Team’s Next HC
Video: 2-7 Texans Look to Land an Upset Against the 4-5 Patriots Sunday
Week 10 Inactives for the Texans and Browns
Texans Place Running Back David Johnson on Injured Reserve
Texans Gab Newsletter
Sign up to receive our daily Texans Gab newsletter, and keep up to date with all the latest Houston Texans news.
We will never share your email address
Fans of Texans Gab
Archives
Select Month
November 2020  (5)
October 2020  (2)
September 2020  (3)
August 2020  (1)
May 2020  (2)
April 2020  (2)
March 2020  (3)
February 2020  (1)
January 2020  (7)
December 2019  (9)
November 2019  (9)
October 2019  (5)
September 2019  (6)
August 2019  (10)
July 2019  (4)
June 2019  (3)
May 2019  (4)
April 2019  (4)
March 2019  (1)
February 2019  (1)
January 2019  (1)
December 2018  (4)
November 2018  (3)
October 2018  (4)
September 2018  (2)
July 2018  (1)
June 2018  (1)
May 2018  (4)
April 2018  (3)
March 2018  (7)
February 2018  (11)
January 2018  (7)
December 2017  (7)
November 2017  (3)
September 2017  (2)
August 2017  (6)
July 2017  (4)
June 2017  (2)
May 2017  (2)
April 2017  (5)
January 2017  (1)
December 2016  (4)
November 2016  (5)
October 2016  (8)
September 2016  (10)
August 2016  (8)
July 2016  (8)
April 2016  (1)
March 2016  (2)
February 2016  (1)
January 2016  (2)
December 2015  (1)
November 2015  (4)
October 2015  (10)
September 2015  (9)
August 2015  (5)
July 2015  (9)
June 2015  (1)
April 2015  (1)
March 2015  (1)
December 2014  (16)
November 2014  (4)
October 2014  (13)
September 2014  (8)
August 2014  (2)
July 2014  (3)
June 2014  (4)
May 2014  (4)
April 2014  (1)
March 2014  (1)
February 2014  (5)
January 2014  (9)
December 2013  (4)
November 2013  (6)
October 2013  (5)
September 2013  (15)
August 2013  (11)
June 2013  (3)
May 2013  (4)
April 2013  (4)
March 2013  (1)
February 2013  (6)
January 2013  (4)
December 2012  (10)
November 2012  (24)
October 2012  (23)
September 2012  (35)
August 2012  (12)
July 2012  (6)
June 2012  (4)
May 2012  (8)
April 2012  (3)
March 2012  (8)
February 2012  (7)
January 2012  (25)
December 2011  (39)
November 2011  (42)
October 2011  (63)
September 2011  (58)
August 2011  (21)
July 2011  (32)
June 2011  (26)
May 2011  (36)
April 2011  (59)
March 2011  (53)
February 2011  (32)
January 2011  (31)
December 2010  (47)
November 2010  (47)
October 2010  (50)
September 2010  (57)
August 2010  (51)
July 2010  (35)
June 2010  (24)
May 2010  (28)
April 2010  (7)
March 2010  (4)
February 2010  (11)
January 2010  (10)
December 2009  (7)
November 2009  (14)
October 2009  (19)
September 2009  (15)
August 2009  (22)
July 2009  (24)
June 2009  (19)
May 2009  (7)
April 2009  (18)
March 2009  (10)
February 2009  (16)
January 2009  (11)
December 2008  (22)
November 2008  (12)
October 2008  (16)
September 2008  (15)
August 2008  (14)
July 2008  (10)
June 2008  (13)
May 2008  (6)
April 2008  (16)
March 2008  (36)
February 2008  (17)
January 2008  (13)
December 2007  (26)
November 2007  (32)
October 2007  (38)
September 2007  (22)
August 2007  (11)
July 2007  (12)
June 2007  (3)
Categories Contests (17)
Fantasy Football (13)
Features (132)
Free Agency (56)
Game Previews (76)
Game Stories (121)
Houston Happenings (10)
Injuries (338)
Main (97)
News (1,324)
NFL Draft (96)
Odds (3)
Opinions (242)
Picks (56)
Police Blotter (9)
Roster Moves (86)
Rumors (19)
Tickets (5)
Video (93)
Sports Gab Network (NFL)
Celebrity Seats has the best Houston Texans Tickets, Houston Astros Tickets, and Houston Rockets Tickets!
Recent Comments
Meta
Log in
Copyright © 2020 Texans Gab - Part of the Sports Gab Network
iMobile Theme created by NewWpThemes.com
Privacy Policy
